<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="apartment_description">
        <item>Now offering in-person, virtual, self-guided tours by appointment!
              To help stop the spread of COVID-19, face masks are required.
              Reach out to us today as helping you find the perfect home remains our priority!
              The Social West Ames is located just west of the Iowa State University campus, providing you with the opportunity to walk, bike, or CyRide to campus with ease.
              The community is also close to many exciting nearby attractions such as West Towne Pub, Kingpin Pizza, Cafe Milo, North Grand Mall, Cinemark Movies 12, and Perfect Games.
              Our one, two, three, four and five-bedroom apartments and townhomes offer spacious floor plans with modern interiors including stainless steel appliances, hardwood flooring, updated cabinetry and countertops, and washers/dryers.
              Residents are invited to relax in our renovated clubhouse, lounge by our two sparkling pools, work out in our fully equipped fitness center, and learn in our private study and conference rooms.
              Social West Ames is a pet friendly community, welcoming both cats and dogs with only a few breed restrictions.
              Call today to schedule a personalized tour and learn why our residents love calling our community home!
        </item>
        <item>We are now accepting in-person tours via scheduled appointments only.
              Our virtual tours are also available.
              Please schedule yours today.
        </item>
        <item>South Meadow Apartments provides 1-3 bedroom apartments for rent.
              All leases include FREE internet, heat, hot water, and an on-site leasing office!
              With several different floor plans to choose from, we are sure we can find the right place for you!
        </item>
        <item>Studio, 1, 2, 3 and 4 bedroom apartments.
              All utilities included.
              Laundry is on-site and free.
              Internet and cable included.
              Close to campus.
              Community gas grill and picnic table.
        </item>
        <item>NOW LEASING FOR FALL 2021: Meet ASPEN! Located just minutes away from Iowa State University, our spacious floor plans are paired with top-notch amenities.
              There’s no doubt about it - Aspen has everything an ISU student will need to live, study, and play!
              We offer a 24-hour fitness center, study lounges, and green spaces for your four-legged friend!
              Hop on one of our two convenient CyRide stops for easy access to everything a Cyclone needs.
              With spacious, furnished bedroom suites and individual private bathrooms, you can socialize or study on your own terms.
              We’re leasing now for the 2020-2021 school year- Call today to schedule a tour and learn why our residents love living at the best community in Ames!
        </item>
        <item>Location, location, location.
              When it comes to location, we are in a prime one in southeast Ames.
              South View Apartments is located on South 5th Street near Duff Avenue, just a few blocks south of Lincoln Way.
              We are a quick 5 minutes from Iowa State University campus, a short bike ride from Squaw Creek Park, and a few steps away from grocery stores, restaurants and shopping.
              Whatever you need, you are within close proximity here at South View Apartments.
              Our apartment community offers two-bedroom apartments in three different sizes, so you can choose the layout that best meets your needs. We are pet friendly and look forward to giving you — and your four-legged friends — a personal tour.
              Call or contact us today to schedule your tour of this great community!
        </item>
        <item>Now offering in-person, virtual, and self-guided tours by appointment!
              To help stop the spread of COVID-19, face masks are required.
              Reach out to us today as helping you find the perfect home remains our priority!
              The Social West Ames is located just west of the Iowa State University campus, providing you with the opportunity to walk, bike, or CyRide to campus with ease.
              The community is also close to many exciting nearby attractions such as West Towne Pub, Kingpin Pizza, Cafe Milo, North Grand Mall, Cinemark Movies 12, and Perfect Games.
              Our one, two, three, four and five-bedroom apartments and townhomes offer spacious floor plans with modern interiors including stainless steel appliances, hardwood flooring, updated cabinetry and countertops, and washers/dryers.
              Residents are invited to relax in our renovated clubhouse, lounge by our two sparkling pools, work out in our fully equipped fitness center, and learn in our private study and conference rooms.
              Social West Ames is a pet friendly community, welcoming both cats and dogs with only a few breed restrictions.
              Call today to schedule a personalized tour and learn why our residents love calling our community home!
        </item>
        <item>South Duff Community Park is a modern, upscale student apartment community serving Iowa State University students, Des Moines Area Community College, and PCI Academy .
              Our premier off-campus apartments are fully furnished with full-size washers and dryers, vaulted ceilings, cable TV, 24-hour gym, game room, and study lounge.
              This beautiful community is surrounded by lush landscape and fields, and only minutes from everything Ames has too offer: Iowa State University, the Jack Trice Stadium, Ames Municipal Airport, and tons of local shopping, dining, and entertainment.
              Come home to South Duff and enjoy a unique living experience like no other in Ames!
        </item>
        <item>Looking for a 1, 2, or 3-bedroom apartment close to the Iowa State University Campus?
              Hunziker Property Management has exactly what you’re looking for! We have hundreds of units within a block of campus.
              Gas,water/sewer, cable, Internet, garbage, lawn care, and snow removal are all included in the rent!
              Hunziker Property Management believes in offering a high-quality living experience and excellent customer service for our tenants.
              We have 24/7 maintenance and do routine building checks to make sure everything is kept at a standard that our tenants deserve.
              Apartments are available now.
              Please contact us to schedule a showing or ask questions about apartments you are interested in.
              We look forward to hearing from you!
        </item>
        <item>Our Somerset apartments are a great option for everyone!
              They are located just around the corner from several local Ames favorites including The Cafe, El Azteca, and +39.
              They are also 8 minutes from campus and close to Cyride stops.
              Management provides gas (heat), water/sewer, basic cable, and upgraded Internet (150 mbps - at most locations).
              Tenants pay for electricity only.
              Buildings have secured entrances, and units come with central A/C, a dishwasher, a microwave, a washer/dryer in unit (some units), and a garage (most units).
              Tenants also have access to the Somerset pool and clubhouse. Undergrads are welcome! Pets friendly units are available!</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>